(Bert:)Thank you very much.
Thanks.
(Leonard:)That is unbelievable.
(Leonard:)Good for Bert.
(Howard:)Damn, the MacArthur
Genius Grant.
(Raj:)Couldn't have happened
to a nicer guy.
(Sheldon:)Everything is stupid
and I want to go home.
(Leonard:)That's Sheldon's way of saying
(Leonard:)he's proud of Bert, too.
(Howard:)Ah.
(Sheldon:)Hey, it's not even called
the "Genius Grant,"
(Sheldon:)it's the MacArthur Fellowship.
(Sheldon:)Just like it's
not Frankenstein,
it's "Frankenstein's Monster."
(Sheldon:)Which brings us back
(Sheldon:)to that hulking
simpleton over there.
(Sheldon:)And if anyone's a genius,
(Sheldon:)it's me for the way
I brought that full circle.
(Leonard:)How much money did he win?
(Raj:)Over half a million dollars.
(Penny:)- Wow.
- And he doesn't have to use it
(Howard:)for research, he can do
whatever he wants with it.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good, maybe he can build
a nicer bridge to live under.
(Howard:)Here he comes.
Right.
(Leonard:)Be polite.
(Sheldon:)I know how to behave.
(Howard:)Do you?
(Sheldon:)Hey,
congratulations Bert!
(Leonard:)Yeah, good for you.
That's amazing.
(Bert:)Thanks.
(Bert:)I was as surprised as anybody.
(Bert:)When they called
and told me
(Bert:)I won, I didn't believe them.
(Bert:)And then they said,
"No, you really won."
And then I said, "Cool."
(Sheldon:)Someone call
George R. R. Martin,
(Sheldon:)this guy knows how
to finish a story.
(Bert:)I've gotten pretty good
at telling it.
(Bert:)Well, see ya.
(Sheldon:)Some genius.
(Sheldon:)I zinged him with sarcasm,
he didn't even notice.
(Leonard:)I know, and it was
(Leonard:)the greatest sarcastic
quip I've ever heard.
(Sheldon:)Well, aren't you a peach.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪